http://sportvideos.com/privacy-statement.html

Home
::
Privacy statement
Printable version
Privacy statement
SportVideos.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to SportVideos.com Web site and governs data collection and usage at all SportVideos.com sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the SportVideos.com Statement of Privacy. SportVideos.com is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy. SportVideos.com is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of your Personal Information
As an E-commerce Web site, SportVideos.com collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by SportVideos.com is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. SportVideos.com does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.SportVideos.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from SportVideos.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the SportVideos.com Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
SportVideos.com and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products
requested. It is possible that SportVideos.com may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from DWS and its affiliates. SportVideos.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.SportVideos.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. SportVideos.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
SportVideos.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. SportVideos.com may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SportVideos.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SportVideos.com, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SportVideos.com or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which SportVideos.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
SportVideos.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control your Personal Information
SportVideos.com offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing sportvideos@gmail.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records. You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from SportVideos.com by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list.
Security of your Personal Information
SportVideos.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through 256 bit encription through thawte.
Changes to this Statement
SportVideos.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how SportVideos.com will use your personal information, SportVideos.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change.
Cart is empty
Categories
Half Price DVD Sale
Baseball DVDs (1)
Basketball DVDs (13)
Billiards DVDs (3)
Bowling DVDs (4)
Boxing DVDs (5)
Cheerleading DVDs (4)
Football DVDs (4)
Golf DVDs (8)
Gymnastics DVDs (6)
Hockey DVDs (4)
Horseshoes DVDs (1)
Ice Skating DVDs (1)
Martial Art DVDs (11)
Physical Education DVDs (5)
Racquetball DVDs (7)
Skateboarding DVDs (1)
Soccer DVDs (9)
Sports Training DVDs (4)
Squash DVDs (1)
Swimming DVDs (3)
Table Tennis DVDs (3)
Tennis DVDs (4)
Track and Field DVDs (3)
Volleyball DVDs (7)
Weight Training DVDs (1)
Wrestling DVDs (2)
Holiday Sale (47)
New Releases (31)
Non-Sport DVDs
Educational for Adults (10)
Educational for Children
Disney Educational DVDs (2)
PBS for Kids DVDs (14)
RocknLearn DVDs (1)
Scholastic (2)
Television (3)
Archery (3)
Badminton (11)
Baseball (9)
Basketball (39)
Billiards (10)
Bowling (11)
Boxing (13)
Cheerleading (11)
ESPN
Field Hockey (16)
Football (15)
Golf (18)
Gymnastics (26)
Hockey (5)
Horseshoes (1)
Ice Skating (1)
Lacrosse (36)
Martial Arts (18)
Physical Education (11)
Racquetball (15)
Skateboarding (3)
Soccer (15)
Softball (18)
Sports Training (9)
Squash (3)
Swimming (14)
Table Tennis (4)
Tennis (10)
Track and Field (7)
Volleyball (20)
Water Polo (7)
Weight Training (5)
Wrestling (7)
Bestsellers
Reading Greens and Making Putts DVD or Download - Free Shipping
$25.00
Learning to Fly: How to Play Above the Rim DVD or Download - Free Shipping
$3.00
Secrets of Successful Golf: How to Break 80 DVD or Download - Free Shipping
$25.00
Badminton Tips and Techniques DVD or Download - Free Shipping
$25.00
Secrets of Successful Golf: How to Break Par DVD or Download - Free Shipping
Need help?
